Guide to the Clark, Hall, and Peck and White Brothers Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- White Brothers, 1880s-1982; Series I
  - New Haven
    - Folded abstracts of title
      - District 22
        - Kimberly Avenue, King Place, Lines Street, West Carlisle Street (Box 182)
        - Columbus Avenue (Box 183)
        - Howard Avenue (Box 184)
        - Button Street (Box 185)
        - Washington Avenue (Even number street addresses 394-398 through 742) (Box 186)
        - DeWitt Street (Box 187)
        - Frank Street (Street addresses 2-6 through 159-161) (Box 188)
        - Frank Street (Street addresses 162 through 196, non-street number files) (Box 189)
        - West Street (Box 190)
        - Lamberton Street (Street addresses 19 through 197-199) (Box 191)
        - Lamberton Street (Street addresses 200 through 215, non-street number files), Terminal Place, Thorn Street (Box 192)
        - Morris Street, Spring Street (Box 193)
        - Putnam Street (Street addresses 143 through 257) (Box 194)
        - Putnam Street (Street addresses 261 through 271, non-street number files), Truman Street (Box 195)
        - Portsea Street, West Portsea Street (Box 196)
        - Rosette Street (Street addresses 61-63 through 215-217) (Box 197)
        - Rosette Street (Street addresses 223 through 227, non-street number files), Truman Street (Box 198)
        - Wilson Street (Box 199)
      - District 23
        - George Street, Meadow Street (Box 200)
        - Prout Street, State Street, Water Street, Whiting Street (Box 201)
      - District 24
        - Chapel Street, Fair Street, Olive Street (Box 202)
        - Prindle Al., Union Street, Union or Long Wharf, Water Street, Wooster Street (Box 203)
        - State Street (Box 204)
      - District 25
        - Brewery Street, Chapel Street, Olive Street (Box 205)
        - Warren Street, Water Street, Wooster Street ("Custom House Square") (Box 206)
      - District 26
        - Brown Street, Water Street, Wooster Street (Box 207)
        - Chapel Street, Chestnut Street, Franklin Street (Box 208)
      - District 27
        - Bridge Street, Collis Street, Hamilton Street (Box 209)
        - Chapel Street, East Street, Water Street (Box 210)
        - Franklin Street, Wallace Street, Wooster Street (Box 211)
      - District 28
        - Academy Street, Chestnut Street, Franklin Street (Box 212)
        - Chapel Street, Wooster Place (Box 213)
        - Court Street, Jefferson Street, Olive Street (Box 214)
        - Grand Avenue (Even number street addresses 762-774 through 930, non-street number files) (Box 215)
        - Olive Street, Greene Street, Hughes Place (Box 216)
        - Street John Street (Box 217)
      - District 29
        - Anderson Street, Avon Street, Bishop Street (Street addresses 7 through 65) (Box 218)
        - Bishop Street (Street addresses 72 through 131-133, non-street number files), Canner Street (Box 219)
        - Bradley Street, Mitchell Drive, Trumbull Street, Willow Street (Box 220)
        - Clark Street (Box 221)
        - Edwards Street (Box 222)
        - Cottage Street, Eld Street (Box 223)
        - Orange Street (East side, odd number street addresses 605-615 through 855-857, non-street number files) (Box 224)
        - Eagle Street, Foster Street (Box 225)
        - Hine Place, Humphrey Street (Box 226)
        - Lawrence Street (Box 227)
        - Nash Street (Box 228)
        - Linden Street, Nicoll Street (Box 229)
        - Mechanic Street, North Bank Street (Box 230)
        - Pearl Street, Pleasant Street (Box 231)
        - Orange Street (East side, odd number street addresses 441 through 875-885) (Box 232)
        - State Street (Even number street addresses 706-708-710 through 898) (Box 233)
        - State Street (Even number street addresses 900-904 through 990-998) (Box 234)
      - District 30
        - Bradley Place, Bradley Street, Jefferson Street, Osborn Street, Pulaski Street (Formerly Sumner Street) (Box 235)
        - Franklin Street, William Street (Box 236)
        - Grand Avenue (North side, odd number street addresses 711-713½ through 995-997-999, non-street number files) (Box 237)
        - Leonard Street, Lyon Street (Box 238)
        - Madison Street, Olive Street (Box 239)
        - State Street (East side, odd number street addresses 517 through 913-919) (Box 240)
      - District 31
        - Beach Street, Humphrey Square, Humphrey Street, Myrtle Street (Box 241)
        - East Street (East side, odd number street addresses 327 through 607) (Box 242)
        - East Street (Even number street addresses 380-558), Franklin Street (East side, odd number street addresses 165 through 247, non-street number files) (Box 243)
        - Grand Avenue (North side, street addresses 531 through 719-721), State Street (Street addresses 907-913 through 1071) (Box 244)
        - Hamilton Street (East side, odd number street addresses 173 through 289-291-293, non-street number files) (Box 245)
        - Hamilton Street (West side, even number street addresses 178-276, non-street number files) (Box 246)
        - Locust Street, Mill River Street, Railroad Avenue, Summer Place, Summer Street, Walnut Street (Box 247)
        - Wallace Street (Box 248)
      - District 32
        - Artizan Street, Chapel Street (Box 249)
        - Olive Street (Box 250)
        - Court Street, Grand Avenue (Atwater block), Street John Street, State Street, Union Street (Box 251)
      - District 33
        - Audubon Street, Avon Street, Bradley Street, Edwards Street, Grove Street (Box 252)
        - Bishop Street, Burns Street, Canner Street, Cold Spring Street (Box 253)
        - Cottage Street, East Rock Road (Box 254)
        - Everit Street, Humphrey Street (Box 255)
        - Lawrence Street, Trumbull Street (Box 256)
        - Willow Street (Box 257)
        - Lincoln Street, Linden Street (Box 258)
        - Livingston Street (Box 259)
        - Orange Street (West side, even number street addresses 338 through 640-642) (Box 260)
        - Orange Street (West side, even number street addresses 644-646 through 858-860-862) (Box 261)
        - Orange Street (West side, non-street number files) (Box 262)
        - Whitney Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 1-21 through 469) (Box 263)
        - Whitney Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 475 through 813-815) (Box 264)
        - Whitney Avenue (East side, non-street number files) (Box 265)
      - District 34
        - Audubon Court, Audubon Street, Grove Street, Orange Street (Box 266)
        - State Street, Trumbull Street (Box 267)
        - Cain Street, East Street (Street addresses 189 through 358) (Box 268)
        - East Street (Non-street number files) (Box 269)
      - District 35
        - Chapel Street, Donnelly Place, Street John Street (Box 270)
        - Franklin Street (East side, odd number street addresses 65 through 139-145, non-street number files), Wallace Street (Even number street addresses 66 through 152, non-street number files) (Box 271)
        - Grand Avenue (Box 272)
        - Greene Street (Box 273)
        - Hamilton Street, Mill River, Railroad Avenue (Box 274)
        - Wallace Street (East side, odd number street addresses 59-61 through 152, non-street number files) (Box 275)
      - District 36
        - Chapel Street, High Street (Box 276)
        - College Street, Crown Street (Box 277)
        - George Street, York Street (Box 278)
      - District 37
        - Center Street, College Street, Crown Street, George Street, Gregson Street, Temple Street (Box 279)
        - Chapel Street (Box 280)
        - Crown Street (Even number street addresses 152-228) (Box 281)
        - Church Street (Box 282)
      - District 38, College Street, Elm Street, Grove Street, High Street, Wall Street, York Street (Box 283)
      - District 39, Church Street, College Street, Elm Street, Grove Street, Temple Street, Wall Street (Box 284)
      - District 40, Chapel Street, Elm Street, High Street, York Street (Box 285)
      - District 41
        - Church Street, Elm Street, Grove Street (Box 286)
        - Orange Street, State Street, Wall Street (Box 287)
      - District 42
        - Center Street, Church Street, George Street (Box 288)
        - Chapel Street (Even number street addresses 756-758 through 866-868) (Box 289)
        - Crown Street (Box 290)
        - State Street (Box 291)
        - Orange Street (Box 292)
      - District 43
        - Church Street, Court Street, Pitkin Street, State Street (Box 293)
        - Chapel Street, (Odd number street addresses 745-751 through 853) (Box 294)
        - Elm Street, Orange Street (Street addresses 134through160) (Box 295)
        - Orange Street (Street addresses 162 through 234, non-street number files) (Box 296)
      - District 50 (Annex)
        - Adeline Street, Alabama Street, Albia Street, Alden Street, Alfred Street, Allen Place, Andress Street, Aner Street, Anthony Drive, Arden Street, Ashland Place (Box 297)
        - Beacon Avenue (Box 298)
        - Assumption Street (Recreation Drive), Chamberlain Street, Chamberlain Place, Chester Street, Clifton Street (Box 299)
        - Barnes Avenue, Beecher Place, Boston Avenue, Bristol Place, Brown Place (Box 300)
        - Burr Street, Burwell Street, Cabot Street, Carroll Street (Box 301)
        - Clarendon Street, Cliff Terrace, Clifford Terrace, Colorado Street, Connecticut Avenue, Cora Street, Cove Street (Street addresses 5 through 88) (Box 302)
        - Cove Street (Street addresses 104 through 211, non-street number files) (Box 303)
        - Concord Street (Box 304)
        - Cranston Street, Crofton Street, Curtiss Place, Daniel Drive, Dean Street (Concord Street), Dell Drive, Donna Drive (Box 305)
        - Douglas Avenue, Lighthouse Point Terrace, Lighthouse Road (Street addresses 175 through 287) (Box 306)
        - Lighthouse Road (Street addresses 300 through 506, non-street number files), Dody Place, Elizabeth Ann Drive (Box 307)
        - Eastern Street, East Shore Parkway, Eden Street, Edgemere Road, Elaine Terrace (Box 308)
        - Eldridge Street, Elmer Street, Emily Road, Essex Street, Essex Turnpike, Ferry Street (Box 309)
        - Fairmont Avenue, Fairview Terrace (Box 310)
        - Fiore Street, First Avenue, Flint Street, Florence Avenue, Foxon Street (Box 311)
        - Farren Avenue, Foxon Blvd., Foxon Road, Foxon Hill Road (Box 312)
        - Forbes Avenue (North side, even number street addresses 20 through 436, non-street number files), Fort Hale Road, Frost Street (Beacon Avenue) (Box 313)
        - Fulton Street, Fulton Terrace (Box 314)
        - Girard Avenue, Glen Haven Road, Goodwin Street (Fulton Street), Grand Avenue (East Grand Avenue) (Box 315)
        - Grannis Place, Hall Street, Harrington Avenue, Hawthorne Road, Hemingway Place (Box 316)
        - Highview Lane, Russell Street (Street addresses 5 through 473-475) (Box 317)
        - Russell Street (Street addresses 505 through 804, non-street number files) (Box 318)
        - Forbes Avenue (South side, odd number street addresses, non-street number files), Morris Causeway, Hills Street, Harding Place, Hervey Street, Hemingway Street (Box 319)
        - Hillside Avenue, Hoover Street, Hopkins Drive, Horsley Avenue, Howard Street (Box 320)
          General
          For Hughes Street Extension, see East Haven. For Hulse Street, see Grand Avenue.
        - Huntington Avenue or Road (Box 321)
        - Ira Street, Irvington Street, John Street, Johnston Street (Box 322)
          For Hyde Street, see Lenox Street.
        - "Kendall Park," Kendall Street, Kingswood Drive, Kneeland Road (Box 323)
          For Kenny Drive, see 1372 Quinnipiac Avenue.
        - Lancraft Street, Laura Lane, Laura Street, LeRoy Terrace, Ley Street, Lincoln Avenue (Box 324)
        - Lenox Street (Box 325)
        - Lexington Avenue (Box 326)
        - Lexington Avenue (Box 327)
        - Main Street, Mansion Street, Marie Street, Marion Street, Massachusetts Avenue, Meadow View Street (Morris Street), Melrose Drive, Milton Street (Box 328)
        - Middletown Avenue, Morris Avenue, Morris Cove Gardens (W. Townsend Avenue), Morris Cove Road, Morris Creek or Dyke (Meadow View Street), Mountain Top Lane, Pequot Street (Box 329)
        - Morse Place, Morse Street (E. Townsend Avenue), Myron Street, Nelson Street, Norwood Road, Oakley Street (Box 330)
        - Ocean View Street, Orchard Avenue, Overlook Street, Oxford Street, Page Street, Palmieri Avenue (Box 331)
        - Pardee Street, Park Lane, Parker Place (Box 332)
        - Pawtucket Street, Peat Meadow Road, Pope Street, Portland Street, Providence Street (Box 333)
          For Phillips Drive, see Marie Street.
        - Quinnipiac Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses through 1099), Oak Ridge Drive (Box 334)
        - Quinnipiac Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses from 1101, non-street number files), "QuinnipiacAvenue Gardens" (Box 335)
        - Quinnipiac Avenue (West side, even number street addresses through 1100) (Box 336)
        - Quinnipiac Avenue (West side, even number street addresses from 1100, non-street number files), Skyview Lane, Sherland Avenue (Box 337)
        - Raynham Road, Revere Street, Rhea Street, Riverview Road, Robertson Street, Rock Hill Road, Roma Street, Roosevelt Street, Roosevelt Ext. (Box 338)
        - Rosewood Avenue, Runo Terrace, Scarboro Street, Shepard Street (Box 339)
        - Shoreham Road (W. Townsend Avenue), Smith Avenue, Sound View Terrace, South End Road, Street Anthony Street, Stewart Street, Stuyvesant Avenue, Terrace Street, Turnor Street (Box 340)
          For Stiles Street, see Waterfront Street.
        - Stratford Avenue, Summit Street, Summit Avenue, Townsend Avenue Developments, Old Shoreham Hotel Land, Parker Land (Box 341)
        - Townsend Avenue (West side, even number street addresses through 900) (Box 342)
        - Townsend Avenue (West side, even number street addresses from 900, non-street number files), Uriah Street, Vale Street (Box 343)
        - Townsend Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 1 through 235) (Box 344)
        - Townsend Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 241 through 873) (Box 345)
        - Townsend Avenue (East side, oddnumber street addressesfrom 911 through 1285, non-street number files) (Box 346)
        - Townsend Terrace, Tuttle Drive, Tuttle Street, Tuttle Street Extension, Upson Street, Upson Terrace (Box 347)
        - Warwick Street, Waterfront Street, Welcome Street, Westminster Street, Weybossett Street, Wheeler Street, Woonsocket Street (Box 348)
        - Woodward Avenue (Box 349)
        - Miscellaneous files for District 50 (Box 350)
      - District 70 (Westville)
        - Alden Avenue (West side, even number street addresses 24-30 through 354, non-street number files), Alston Avenue, Amity Road (Box 351)
        - Alden Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 7 through 361-371, non-street number files) (Includes William H. Alden deeds), Anthony Street (Edgewood Development Co.) (Box 352)
          Alden Avenue (East side) includes William H. Alden deeds.
        - Austin Street, Bank Street, Barnett Street, Benton Street, Beverly Road, Birch Drive (Box 353)
        - Blake Street, Brooklawn Circle, Burton Street, Byron Place, Cleveland Road, Colonial Place, Conrad Drive (Box 354)
        - Central Avenue (Odd number street addresses 239 through 607-609) (Box 355)
        - Central Avenue (Even number street addresses 188-194 through 608), Curtis Drive (Box 356)
        - Chapel Street (Old Cavan Street files) (Box 357)
        - Davis Street, Dayton Street, Derby Avenue, Earle Street, East Ramsdell Place, East Ramsdell Street, Edgewood Way, Elmwood Road, Emerson Street, Englewood Drive (Box 358)
        - Edgewood Avenue (Box 359)
          Includes Donald G. Mitchell property, Eberth and Rowley deeds, Elm City Nursery Development.
        - Fairfield Street, Farnham Street, Field Street, Fowler Street, Frederick Street, Genesee Street, Glen View Street, Green Hill Terrace, Hard Street, Harper Avenue (Box 360)
        - Forest Road (Box 361)
        - Fountain Street (South side, even number street addresses 6 through 290-310) (Box 362)
        - Fountain Street (South side, even number street addresses 326 through 530, non-street number files) (Box 363)
        - Fountain Street (North side, odd number street addresses 33-35 through 689) (Box 364)
        - Fountain Street (non-street number files), Fountain Terrace, Harrison Street (Box 365)
        - Hemlock Road, Hilltop Road, Judwin Avenue, Kenter Place (Box 366)
        - Knollwood Avenue, Kohary Drive, Lakeview Terrace, Laurel Road (Box 367)
        - Lawncrest Road, Ramsdell Place, Ramsdell Street (Box 368)
        - Ray Road, Richmond Avenue, Robin Lane, Rock Creek Road, Roger Road, Roger Street (Box 369)
        - Long Hill Terrace, Lowin Avenue, Maplewood Road, Marlin Drive, Marvel Road, Marvelwood Drive (Box 370)
        - Morton Lane, Mountain Road (Formerly Julius Street), Mumford Road, Oliver Road, Pardee Place, Philip Street, Pine Rock Avenue, Plant Street, Robin Lane (Formerly Miles Street) (Box 371)
        - McKinley Avenue, Pond Lily Avenue (Box 372)
        - Seneca Road, Spenser Place, Springside Avenue, Stevenson Road, Stone Street, Strong Street (Box 373)
        - Taylor Avenue, Tour Avenue, Tyron Street, Vista Terrace (Box 374)
        - Valley Place North, Valley Place South, Valley Street (Street addresses 106 through 633) (Box 375)
        - Valley Street (Non-street number files), Parkside Drive (Box 376)
        - Victory Drive, Willard Street (Box 377)
        - Yale Avenue (Box 378)
        - Westbrook Lane, West Elm Street, Westerleigh Road (Box 379)
        - West Prospect Street, "Westville Park" (S. Fountain Street), Whittier Road, Wintergreen Avenue, Woodbridge Avenue, Woodbridge Street, "Woodside Terrace," Wright Avenue (Box 380)
        - West Rock Avenue (Box 381)
        - Whalley Avenue (South side,streetaddresses 838 through 1136-1138) (Box 382)
        - Whalley Avenue (South side, street addresses 1150 through 1534) (Box 383)
        - Whalley Avenue (South side, street addresses from 1540, non-street number files) (Box 384)
        - Westwood Road, Whalley Avenue (North side, street addresses 827 through 1155) (Box 385)
        - Whalley Avenue (North side, street addresses 1255 through 1375, non-street number files), Woodside Terrace (Box 386)
    - Plot map book for Fair Haven addresses (Box 387)
      - Map (District) 100, Plots 1-48 (Box 388)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on Albert Street, Lyman Street, State Street, Welton Street.
      - Map (District) 101, Plot 1 (Box 389)
      - Map (District) 102, Plots 1-45 (Box 389)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on Ash Street, Birch Street, Grace Street, Ridge Street, Sycamore Street, View Street.
      - Map (District) 103
        - Plots 1-50 (Box 390)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Cedar Hill Avenue, Grace Street, May Street, Ridge Street, Rock Street, State Street, Warren Place.
        - Plots 51-97 (Box 391)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Cedar Hill Avenue, May Street, Ridge Street, Rock Street, State Street, Warren Place.
      - Map (District) 104, Plots 1-45 (Box 392)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Bailey Street, Clinton Avenue, Fawn Street, Middletown Avenue, Rowe Street
      - Map (District) 105, Plots 1-2 (Box 393)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on Clinton Avenue, Middletown Avenue.
      - Map (District) 106, Plots 1-24 (Box 393)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on Mechanic Street, State Street, View Street.
      - Map (District) 107 (Box 393)
        - Plots 1-25
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Jackson Street, Lombard Street, Main Street, Monroe Street, Old Ferry Path, Peck Street, State Street, View Street.
        - Plots 26-81 (Box 394)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Cedar Hill Avenue, Lombard Street, Main Street, Peck Street, View Street, Warren Place.
      - Map (District) 108
        - Plots 1-50 (Box 395)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Cedar Hill Avenue, Ferry Street, Lombard Street, Peck Street, State Street, Warren Place.
        - Plots 51-93 (Box 396)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Ferry Street, Fillmore Street, Fox Street, Jackson Street, Lombard Street, Peck Street, State Street.
      - Map (District) 109
        - Plots 1-50 (Box 397)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Clinton Avenue, Dover Street, English Street, Ferry Street, Lombard Street, Maltby Street, Peck Street, Rowe Street.
        - Plots 51-125 (Box 398)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Bailey Street, Clinton Avenue, Dover Street, English Street, Ferry Street, Lombard Street, Peck Street, Rowe Street.
        - Plots 126-157 (Box 399)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Clinton Avenue, Dover Street, English Street, Ferry Street, Lombard Street, Peck Street, Rowe Street, Wilcox Place.
      - Map (District) 110, Plots 1-67 (Box 400)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on Bailey Street, Dover Street, Downing Street, Front Street, Lombard Street, Maltby Street, Middletown Avenue, Peck Street, Quinnipiac Street
      - Map (District) 112, Plots 1-2 (Box 400)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on James Street, State Street.
      - Map (District) 115, Plots 1-46 (Box 401)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on Grand Avenue, Haven Street, Locust Street, Market Street, Mill River Street, Walnut Street.
      - Map (District) 122, Plot 1 (Box 401)
        Includes abstract of title for a property on Chapel Street.
      - Map (District) 126
        - Plots 1-60 (Box 402)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Fillmore Street, Pine Street, Poplar Street.
        - Plots 61-110 (Box 403)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, James Street, Main Street, Market Street, Monroe Street, Pine Street.
        - Plots 111-150 (Box 404)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Alton Street, Castle Street, Fillmore Street, Lombard Street, Main Street,Market Street, Monroe Street.
        - Plots 151-193 (Box 405)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Alton Street, Blatchley Avenue, Castle Street, Fillmore Street, James Street, Lombard Street, Main Street, Market Street, Pine Street, Poplar Street.
      - Map (District) 127
        - Plots 1-60 (Box 406)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Chatham Street, Ferry Street, Grafton Street, Pine Street, Poplar Street, Rowe Street.
        - Plots 61-120 (Box 407)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Chatham Street, Clinton Avenue,GraftonStreet, Ferry Street, Limerick Street, Lombard Street, Pine Street, Rowe Street.
        - Plots 121-184 (Box 408)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Chatham Street, Clinton Avenue, Ferry Street, Grafton Street, Lombard Street, Pine Street, Poplar Street, Rowe Street.
      - Map (District) 128
        - Plots 1-50 (Box 409)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Chatham Street, Clinton Avenue, Downing Street, Front Street, Grafton Street, Lombard Street, Maltby Street, Downing Street, Pine Street.
        - Plots 51-97 (Box 410)
      - Map (District) 129
        - Plots 1-60 (Box 411)